字幕出自 Netflix，提前 16 秒对应 BD Subtitles from Netflix, 16 seconds ahead for BD Netflixの字幕、BDは16秒先読 み
字幕出自 Netflix，提前 16 秒对应 BD Subtitles from Netflix, 16 seconds ahead for BD Netflixの字幕、BDは16秒先読 み
Something flashed.
有東西在發光
Is that so?
是嗎？
Then this is where we part.
那我們就在這裡分道揚鑣吧
Excuse me, but I'm in a hurry.
我在趕時間，先告辭了
You bastard better not get too cocky.
你們這些傢伙別太狂妄了
If you want to leave, wash your asses in the river
想走的人可以帶東西直接過河
and line up behind Thorkell.
排隊去找托魯克爾
That'll settle everything.
這樣就解決了吧
Thorkell doesn't want our asses. It's the prince's.
托魯克爾要的不是我們，而是王子
Now, Askeladd.
喂，阿謝拉特
We've served you for years. We'd rather not kill you.
我們跟了你這麼久，我們並不想殺你
Leave us the prince and disappear.
把王子留下，你們快離開吧
Avalon?
阿瓦隆？
Is that the name of a land?
那是地名嗎？
Yes.
對
The name of a paradise.
那是樂園的名字
Your great ancestor Lord Artorius…
你偉大的祖先阿托利斯大人
He is in that land.
就在那裡
But Mother,
但是媽媽
Lord Artorius is a legendary general from a long time ago.
阿托利斯不是很久以前的將軍嗎？
Is he really still alive?
他還活著嗎？
Avalon is
阿瓦隆
a far off distant land, beyond the western sea.
位在遙遠西方大海的另一頭
It is an island where fairies live and spring is eternal.
那個島上住著妖精，四季如春
It is a land where no one ages or dies.
那是個沒有生老病死的世界
That is where
他在那裡治療在戰爭時受的傷
Once he is healed,
等到康復後
Lord Artorius
阿托利斯大人
will return to us from that distant land…
就會回到我們身邊
and deliver us from our suffering.
並將我們從痛苦中解救出來
When that time comes,
那個時候來臨時
you must serve him.
你一定要侍奉他
He is the true king and a great warrior.
他才是真正的國王、真正的戰士
Become his wisdom.
成為他的智囊
Become his sword.
當他的劍
Someday…
總有一天…
May I speak
道別之前
before saying goodbye?
我能說幾句話嗎？
There's no point..
說什麼都沒用
We have spent a long time together over the years.
我跟你們相處了這麼久
We've celebrated
一起歡笑
and drank together.
一起喝酒
We've waded through the carnage of battle.
一起出生入死好幾次
But there is something I have kept from you.
有件事我一直沒告訴你們
For the entire decade we have spent together…
和你們在一起的這十幾年
I have despised you from the very bottom of my heart.
我打從心底厭惡你們
Pigs are better than you imbecile Danes.
你們這些蠢丹麥人連豬都不如
Damn it!
可惡！
Get the prince!
抓住王子！
Thorfinn!
托爾芬！
Hold on to something, brats!
小鬼們，抓穩了！
We're leaving!
要衝了！
Damn you!
可惡！
Damn it. They saw this coming.
可惡，被他們料到了
After them! Don't let them escape!
快追，別讓他們跑了！
Go!
快點！
Not if I have anything to do with it!
我不會讓你得逞的！
Forget him! Go after the sled!
別管他，去追雪橇！
Go!
快！
My men are so predictable.
真不愧是我的手下
You've assessed the situation well.
情勢判斷得很準確
Now then…
那麼…
This isn't looking good for me.
看來我遇上麻煩了
Seems you've lost faith in me.
你們似乎對我沒有信心
I can't make it out from here.
太遠了看不清楚
But they seem to be arguing.
但他們好像打起來了
They're having a falling out.
起內訌了吧
It happens in these situations.
這種時候經常會發生這種事
-Pathetic. -Everyone's scared of dying these days.
-真可悲 -最近大家都很怕死
This is truly disgraceful!
這太不像話了！
How could they start a fight without me?
打架怎麼可以少了我？
-That's what bothers you? -Don't start without me!
-你不滿的是這個？ -讓我加入吧
Surround them!
包圍他們！
Take out the horses!
把馬殺掉！
What are you waiting for? Kill them, Thorfinn!
你在做什麼？托爾芬，快幹掉他們！
Throw your knives!
把刀丟出去！
Shut up! I have nothing to throw!
吵死了，沒有東西可以丟了！
Damn it. Askeladd isn't coming.
可惡，阿謝拉特沒來
What the hell is that geezer doing?
那個禿頭在搞什麼？
Stop, Bjorn!
表倫，停下來
Listen to us!
聽我們說
Do you take me for a fool to think I'd stop?
你叫我停，我就停嗎？
Me of all people?
你當我是誰？
Think about it, Bjorn!
表倫，想想看
Our survival depends on how we use the prince!
我們的生死 取決於我們利用王子的方式
It's pointless, Atli!
沒用的，亞托利
Bjorn is Askeladd's right-hand man!
表倫是阿謝拉特的左右手
You won't persuade him!
你不可能勸得了他
We have to kill him!
我們必須殺了他！
That's right! He's starting to get it.
沒錯，你們很懂嘛
Askeladd left the prince in my care because he trusts me.
阿謝拉特信任我，才把王子交給我
If you want to take the prince,
要想從我手上搶走王子
then come at me, you cowards!
就放馬過來，一群懦夫！
Wait, stop! I told you to attack me!
等等，我叫你們放馬過來！
Not the horses!
不是殺馬！
Hey, wait!
等…
We're flipping over!
要翻車了！
Hey! Thorfinn's getting away!
喂，托爾芬跑掉了！
Let him go!
沒關係，讓他走！
Prince, are you alive?
王子，你還活著嗎？
Don't be so reckless!
你別亂來
-Prince! -Think first!
-王子，喂！ -想一下再行動
He's alive.
他還活著
All right, let's go back.
好，我們回去吧
You cowards aren't gonna come after me?
你們這些廢物，不放馬過來嗎？
You survived too, Bjorn?
你也還活著啊，表倫？
That mushroom!
那個蘑菇
You should attack all at once.
一起攻過來吧！
I'll send you to Valhalla as a group!
我會送你們一起去瓦爾哈拉
Damn it!
可惡！
That geezer's such a pain in the ass!
那個光頭真會給我找麻煩！
Don't die before I can kill you,
在我殺了你之前可別死啊
Askeladd!
阿謝拉特！
Good grief.
真是的
How tedious old age is.
歲月不饒人
To think that I, Askeladd,
沒想到阿謝拉特我
can't see a way out, being surrounded by a mere 50 men.
連區區50人的包圍都無法突破
Pace yourself. Wait for the right time to escape.
我要等待逃走的時機
Thorkell's army will be here soon.
托魯克爾的人馬很快就到了
They'll  wreak havoc.
到時候一定會一片混亂
That hurt, you little shit!
痛死了，你這臭小子！
I did.
看到了
Right through the helmet.
連頭盔都…
I couldn't even do that with an ax.
我連用斧頭都沒辦法砍成那樣
Damn, he's still as strong as ever.
可惡，他還是跟以前一樣強
Damn it.
可惡，我發脾氣了
Come on guys, I'm sorry for yelling.
抱歉剛剛對你們大吼大叫
Come now.
過來吧
This old man isn't angry anymore.
大叔我已經不生氣了
You on the east side! Get back or you'll be hit with an arrow!
東邊的人都閃開，不然會被箭射到！
Here come the arrows.
拿出弓箭了
Torgrim!
托爾古里！
You in charge?
這是你帶頭的嗎？
So what if I am, you old geezer!
是又怎樣？你這老不死的傢伙！
You sure about this?
你確定要這樣嗎？
You could kill me.
你可以殺了我
I don't care!
我不在乎！
Bjorn and Thorfinn are highly skilled.
表倫和托爾芬都很強
They might have killed your pursuers.
追殺他們的話，被殺的會是你們
If that's the case, you'll need my help retrieving the prince.
那樣的話
If you take me hostage,
如果拿我當人質
Bjorn would come back to trade the prince for me.
表倫一定會帶著王子回來跟我交換
But that's only if I'm alive.
前提是我還活著的話
What do we do, Torgrim?
托爾古里，該怎麼辦？
Aim for his legs.
射他的腿
We got him!
中了
This isn't like you, Askeladd.
阿謝拉特，你平常不會這樣的
You've never been such a desperate man.
你從來就不是那麼拚命的人吧
If the risk outweighed the reward, you'd always withdraw from a fight.
如果風險大於獎賞 你以前一定會放棄
So why risk your life for that coward prince now?
幹嘛為了那種窩囊王子賭上性命？
Do you plan to be buried with your reward?
你打算想把獎賞帶到墳墓去嗎？
I'm an old man.
我老了
I don't have a lot of time left to work in comfort.
能輕鬆賺錢的時間不多了
So naturally…
所以我當然
I can't wait any longer.
沒辦法再等了
I can't keeping waiting for the true king to return from Avalon.
我等不到真正的國王從阿瓦隆歸來了
I don't get it. What's he talking about?
我不知道他在說什麼
Enough. Apprehend him.
夠了，解決他吧
What are you waiting…
喂，怎麼了？
Hey there.
喂，你們玩得開心嗎？
Which one of you is the leader Askeladd?
首領阿謝拉特是哪位？
I most certainly want to meet him.
我很想見見他
You're in trouble.
這可麻煩了
Now, we've got an unexpected visitor.
意外的訪客來了
Yep.
你真的好高大
Now that I see you up close.
近看更是如此
My name is Torgrim.
我叫托爾古里
We won't fight.
我不會反抗
Please hear me out.
請聽我說
Commander!
老大！
The prince isn't here.
王子不在這裡
That's right!
是的！
That's what I wanted to tell you.
我正想跟你說這件事
We were planning to hand the prince over to you.
我們本來打算把王子交給你
But our leader, Askeladd, let him escape.
但首領阿謝拉特把王子放了
But don't worry!
不過別擔心！
We've got ten skilled men pursuing him.
我派了十個高手去追了
Either way, please let us handle the prince.
總之，王子的事就交給我們
In the name of Odin, we will surely capture him!
我以奧丁之名發誓，一定把他抓回來
We've got other advantages too.
而且我還有其他王牌
As I was saying…
等一下，喂
So you're Askeladd?
你就是阿謝拉特？
You look like a wise man.
看起來很聰明嘛
By the way,
對了
I don't see Thorfinn. Where is he?
我沒看到托爾芬
Did you kill him?
你把他殺了嗎？
I didn't kill him.
沒有
I had him protect the prince.
我派他保護王子
He's nothing to do with this mutiny.
他沒有參與這場叛變
Is that so?
是嗎？
I'm relieved to hear that.
那我就放心了
All right.
好
You goons have waited long enough!
混混們，讓你們久等了
Except for Askeladd,
除了阿謝拉特
kill them all!
其他人都殺掉！
This wasn't supposed to happen, Torgrim!
這和說好的不一樣，托爾古里
Come on, guys.
喂，你們
Pick up your weapons.
武器拿起來
You should die like warriors.
至少要死得像戰士吧
Hurry up. Come on.
快點啊
I'm saying this for your own sake.
我是為了你們好
You won't go to Valhalla if you die unarmed.
手無寸鐵地死掉就去不了瓦爾哈拉了
Damn it!
可惡！
All right. This is more like it.
很好，就是要這樣
Wait, Thorkell!
等一下，托魯克爾
Are you sure this is what you want?
你確定要這樣嗎？
If you kill us, you won't get the prince!
殺了我們，就抓不到王子了
You know, I'm sure I'll capture him on my own.
我確定
Here. Take your ax.
來，你的斧頭
Come at me.
來吧
Try to feel good about your death as a warrior.
身為戰士，能夠戰死應該要很高興
One, two, three, four.
一、二、三、四…
I feel for you, Torgrim.
我很同情你，托爾古里
-From the bottom of my-- -Shut up!
-打從心底… -閉嘴！
This is all your fault!
這一切都是你的錯！
Give it up, Torgrim.
放棄吧，托爾古里
You're good as dead.
你跟死人沒兩樣
You're going to die for sure.
你死定了
So you might as well go out fighting, right?
既然這樣，不如就死得壯烈一點吧？
Le me help you.
我來幫你
Now, fight me.
放馬過來啊
Come on.
來吧
Attack me.
攻擊我啊
Oh my.
情況不妙
I over did it this time, didn't I?
難道我給他太大的壓力了嗎？
He's no good.
不行了
He's lost his spirit.
魂都飛了
Hello?
喂…
What's that?
那是什麼？
A horse?
馬？
Thorfinn!
托爾芬！
Here we go!
好耶！
Greetings, Thorfinn!
喂，托爾芬！
You seem well.
你看起來很有精神
Don't touch Askeladd!
不准碰阿謝拉特！
He's my prey!
他是我的獵物！
If you lay a finger on him, I'll kill you!
敢動他一根寒毛，我就殺了你！
You got that, giant?
聽懂了嗎，大塊頭？
Touch him and you die!
敢碰他，你就死定了！
I…
我…
I knew he was an idiot.
我早就知道他很笨
And now this mouse is picking a fight with a bear.
但這隻小老鼠竟然跟一頭大熊挑釁
Your prey?
你的獵物？
Isn't this guy your boss?
他不是你的首領嗎？
He's not my boss!
他才不是我的首領！
Did you hear that? That kid's out to fight the commander.
喂，你聽到了嗎？那孩子想殺了首領
If that's true, he really is fearless.
真的嗎？他膽子真大
Give Askeladd to me.
把阿謝拉特交出來
If you don't, I'll kill you.
不然我就殺了你
Really?
真的嗎？
Then I won't hand him over.
那我偏不給
Did you hear that?
你們聽到了嗎？
Thorfinn and I will be fighting a duel to decide which one of us gets Askeladd!
我和托爾芬要決鬥 看阿謝拉特歸誰的！
You are all witnesses!
你們都是證人！
-All right! -Kill him!
-好耶！ -殺了他！
Bastard. Deciding that on his own.
混蛋，竟然自作主張…
Thorfinn.
托爾芬
If you win, I'll let him go.
如果你贏了，我就放你們走
I'll even give you a horse.
還附送一匹馬
Trust me. This won't go like it did back in London.
別以為你會像在倫敦那樣走運
I would expect nothing less
我很期待呢
from the son of Thors…
托爾茲之子
last descendant of a great warrior family!
戰士家族的末裔！